Guide to the Central Washington University Relations. Photographs, Slides and Negatives 1950s-2000
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Athletes Photos, Football, Basketball, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 34-13)
- Faculty, Physical therapy, Personnel, Student Life, Campus, 1990- (Box-folder 34-14)
- Dr. Knight Manuscript, Foreign Language Department Correspondence, 1997-; rg270610 (Box-folder 35-1)
- Sociology Colloquium Development: The Approaching Millennium: America prepares for Armageddon, 1996- (Box-folder 35-2)
- Resolutions, Development: Board of Trustees, 1997- (Box-folder 35-3)
- Brochure, Study Abroad, International Studies, 1996- (Box-folder 35-4)
- Student Guides, Estimate Costs, 1995- (Box-folder 35-5)
- Award Winning Poet Poster, 1996- (Box-folder 35-6)
- Parents Association Logo Development, 1996- (Box-folder 35-7)
- In Focus Newsletter Development, 1996- (Box-folder 35-8)
- Manastash Brochure Development, 1996- (Box-folder 35-9)
- Brochure College of the Science Lecture Series, 1996- (Box-folder 35-10)
- Brochure Ronald E. McNair Scholarship, 1995- (Box-folder 35-11)
- Brochure Alumni Postcard, 1995- (Box-folder 35-12)
- Library Signs, Staff Association, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 35-13)
- Brochure Elementary Education Collaborative Program, 1998- (Box-folder 35-14)
- Washington Writers English Journal, 1997- (Box-folder 35-15)
- Brochure CWU Sampler Card, 1997- (Box-folder 35-16)
- Women's Studies Brochure, 1995- (Box-folder 35-17)
- Continuing Education, 1997- (Box-folder 35-18)
- USEL Brochure, 1994- (Box-folder 35-19)
- Writer Workshop, 1996- (Box-folder 35-20)
- Visitor's Guide Brochure, 1995- (Box-folder 35-21)
- Business After Hours Brochure, 1996- (Box-folder 35-22)
- Theater Summer Session, Brochure, 1998- (Box-folder 35-23)
- Study Abroad Brochure, 1997- (Box-folder 35-24)
- CWU Associates Logo Development, Brochures, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 35-25)
- Construction Management Brochure, 1996- (Box-folder 35-26)
- X-mas Cards for President's Office, 1994- (Box-folder 35-27)
- Poster for Theater Arts Production, Robin Hood, 1996- (Box-folder 35-28)
- Forum Poster: The Kittitas Community- Place, Home, Community, 1996- (Box-folder 35-29)
- Central Investment Fund, 1995- (Box-folder 35-30)
- Deborah Butterfield Sculpture Dedication, 1995- (Box-folder 36-1)
- School of Business and Economics Honors Banquet poster, 1996- (Box-folder 36-2)
- Sarah Spurgeon Art Gallery Poster, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 36-3)
- Athletic Training at CWU, 1987- (Box-folder 36-4)
- Affirmative Action Poster, Sexual Harassment Brochure, 1994- (Box-folder 36-5)
- Tickets, Community Planning Forum, 1996- (Box-folder 36-6)
- Centennial Brochure, 1991- (Box-folder 36-7)
- Campus Building Plans, Layouts, 1970-1996 (Box-folder 36-8)
- Studio/Photo Development Correspondence, 1996- (Box-folder 36-9)
- CHCI, Reslife, Department of Music, 1990-2000 (Box-folder 36-10)
- Friends of Washoe Gala, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 36-11)
- Campus Apartment Calendar, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 37-1)
- Moore Hall, Residence Hall Logo Art, Advisory, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 37-2)
- Residence Hall Logo Art Beck, Davies, Meisner, Muzzall, Munson, Quigley, Sparks, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 37-3)
- Residence Hall Drawings, 1986- (Box-folder 37-4)
- Thanksgiving Drawing, 1990- (Box-folder 38-1)
- Dining Services Drawing, 1990- (Box-folder 38-2)
- Education Week Brochure, 1996- (Box-folder 38-3)
- Language and Geography Poster Development, 1990- (Box-folder 38-4)
- Flight Tech Aviation program, 1997- (Box-folder 38-5)
- Friends of Washoe Art, 2000- (Box-folder 38-6)
- William O. Douglas Recital Poster, 1996- (Box-folder 38-7)
- Auxiliary Department Art. (Box-folder 38-8)
- Drama Teacher Summer Institute, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 38-9)
- CHCI Posters, no date- (Box-folder 38-10)
- Reslife, CHCI, Yearbook Draft, Theater, no date- (Box-folder 39-1)
- Panoramic Campus, no date- (Box-folder 39-2)
- Reslife, Senior Ventures, Campus, 1990- (Box-folder 39-3)
- completed projects, no date- (Box-folder 40 -1)
- master software books, no date- (Box-folder 40 -2)
- the SyQuest archive, no date- (Box-folder 40 -3)
- priority one set, no date- (Box-folder 40 -4)
- Part 1 Full Backup II, no date- (Box-folder 40 -5)
- #6, no date- (Box-folder 40 -6)
- #7, no date- (Box-folder 40 -7)
- #8, no date- (Box-folder 40 -8)
- #9, no date- (Box-folder 40 -9)
- #11, no date- (Box-folder 40 -10)
- #13, no date- (Box-folder 40 -11)
- #14, no date- (Box-folder 40 -12)
- #15, no date- (Box-folder 40 -13)
- #16, no date- (Box-folder 40 -14)
- #17, no date- (Box-folder 40 -15)
- #18, no date- (Box-folder 40 -16)
- #19, no date- (Box-folder 40 -17)
- #20, no date- (Box-folder 40 -18)
- Softball photos CD, 2002- (Box-folder 40 -19)
- Commencement Photos CD, 2004- (Box-folder 40 -20)
- Softball photos CD, 2002- (Box-folder 40 -21)
- Commencement Photos CD, 2004- (Box-folder 40 -22)
- CWU Photos, 2003- (Box-folder 40 -23)
- Jaz (disk) #1 CWU Graphics Productions, 2001- (Box-folder 40-1)
- Jaz (disk) #2 CWU Graphics Productions, 2002- (Box-folder 40-2)
- CWU Graphics Production #2, 2002- (Box-folder 40-3)
- CWU Graphics Productions, no date- (Box-folder 40-4)
- Periodic Table, no date- (Box-folder 40-5)
- Jaz disk, no date- (Box-folder 40-6)
- Jaz disk, no date- (Box-folder 40-7)
- Jaz disk, no date- (Box-folder 40-8)
- Classroom -IET Class at Kittitas Valley Wind Farm, Vijay Singh Working With Jazz Choir, 2010- (Box-folder 41-1)
- Miscellaneous -Miller, 08/2010 Judy Retirement Party; Mumma, 11/2010 Amy Wine Class, Melbourne; Tim Nat/Geo Shoot; Nutrition Students at Fish Food Bank; Student Teachers (Box-folder 41-2)
- Commencement - Disc 1, 2010- (Box-folder 41-3)
- Commencement - Disc 2, 2010- (Box-folder 41-4)
- Commencement - Disc 3, 2010- (Box-folder 41-5)
- Commencement - Disc 4, 2010- (Box-folder 41-6)
- College of Business - Extreme Entrepreneur, Boeing Field Meeting, Ware Fair Fundraiser, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 41-7)
- Classroom Fall -Bruce Palmquist: Egg Drop at Tomlinson Field, Lind Hall Physics Class, 2010- (Box-folder 41-8)
- Miscellaneous Fall -Sokol, Nick- Playing Sax in Concert Hall; Students Wearing Folding Hats; Welcome Center Twilight Shots, 2010- (Box-folder 41-9)
- Miscellaneous - Campus Science Building Art, Sky with Trees; Employee Service Awards; Orchestra Rehearsals in Formals, 2010- (Box-folder 41-10)
- Teaching Classroom -Airth, Paula: Graphic Design, Bennet: Nutrition F.I.S.H. Food Bank/ Nutrition Students, Rubin, Charlie: Fishbowl with Students and Student Teachers, 2010- (Box-folder 41-11)
- Miscellaneous - Student Teacher Labs, Winter Campus, 2010- (Box-folder 41-12)
- Classroom - Tim Sorey chemistry Class, Student Teacher Labs, 2010- (Box-folder 41-13)
- Miscellaneous Fall - 10/2010 Alumni Banquet, 10/2010 Kiessling, Ann, 10/2010 River Clean-up 2010 Classroom-Bennet Nutrition Class, Palmquist Physics Class: Egg Drop, Light, Rubin Fishbowl Group Study (Box-folder 41-14)
- Events Fall - Bite of the Burg, Gaudino CWU Shirts to Chamber, Kittitas County Fair, 2010- (Box-folder 41-15)
- Miscellaneous Fall - Elementary School Students Science; Hanseg, Sig; Jazz Nutcracker, 2010- (Box-folder 41-16)
- Movers and Shakers RA Group Portraits, no date- (Box-folder 41-17)
- Events - Carmina Burana: CWU Music at Benaroya Hall, 2010- (Box-folder 41-18)
- A Trip to the top: Photos by John Foster; Basketball at National Tournament, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 41-19)
- Campus Fall Disc 2, 2010- (Box-folder 41-20)
- Miscellaneous - Dining Cinco De Mayo Food Shot, Coaches Coffee, NT Student Extracted Headshots, Palouse Farmland, Chris Smart Photos, Rock Wall Climbers, 07/2010 Welcome Center Ribbon Climbing Wall: College Students, Little Cats-Children (Box-folder 41-21)
- Class/Students: Lubinski, Pat Field Class; Fun Students on Campus, 2010- (Box-folder 41-22)
- Events CEC Showcase of Action; Peter Gries Retirement Reception; Ralph Nader, 2010- (Box-folder 41-23)
- College of Business 35th Anniversary Banquet, 2010- (Box-folder 41-24)
- Miscellaneous Events Disc 2: Deep Sea Daze, Garibaldi, David performance, Health Fair, MLK March, Mochi making on SURC patio, 2010- (Box-folder 41-25)
- Discover Disk 1, 2010- (Box-folder 41-26)
- Discover Disk 2, 2010- (Box-folder 41-27)
- OPR: Alpine Tower, 2010- (Box-folder 41-28)
- Miscellaneous Fall: Pizza with the Police, Pigskin Flag Football, Christmas Dinner in Holmes, 2010- (Box-folder 41-29)
- Fred Meyer Night, 2010- (Box-folder 41-30)
- Wellington's Wildfire, 2010- (Box-folder 41-31)
- Miscellaneous Fall: 11/2010 IET Job Fair, Jayanthi, 10/2010 Raman Dance Co., 10/2010 MCA IET Gift Presentation, Freshman Move in 09/2010, 10/2010 Sanz Crickette Presentation (Box-folder 41-32)
- Campus Fall Disc 1, 2010- (Box-folder 41-33)
- Hats on White: Students on White background with Hats, 2010- (Box-folder 41-34)
- Hats! Students and Stack/ McConnell Columns Studio Wheel Shots, 2010- (Box-folder 41-35)
- Miscellaneous Fall: I-90 Business Signs, Highway 10 Mileposts, Wheels on Campus- Bike and Board, 2010- (Box-folder 41-36)
- Film Strip Shots (Box-folder 41-37)
- Source Disc 1, 2011- (Box-folder 41-38)
- Mammoth Site Atlas, 2008- (Box-folder 41-39)
- Bite of the Burg NS and RV, 2008- (Box-folder 41-40)
- Source Disc 2, 2011- (Box-folder 41-41)
- Crystal Apple Award, 2011- (Box-folder 41-42)
- Commencement Disc 1, 2011- (Box-folder 41-43)
- Commencement Disc 2: General James Mattis, 2011- (Box-folder 41-44)
- Commencement Disc 2: Commencement Student Speaker Reception, 2011- (Box-folder 414-45)
- PESH Nicholson Shoot: Studio Light on location Shooting, Students and HS Students Together, 2011- (Box-folder 41-46)
- Pat O`Shaughnessy Roast Disc 1, 2011- (Box-folder 41-47)
- Pat O`Shaughnessy Roast Disc 2, 2011- (Box-folder 41-48)
- Events Fall: Kamola 100 Year Celebration, CWU Open House, Pep Rally, Ware Fare, 2011- (Box-folder 41-49)
- Miscellaneous Spring: Career Quest, Family Weekend Pigs Hit-n-Run, IET AGS Check Ceremony, Wildcat Day, 2011- (Box-folder 41-50)
- Miscellaneous Fall: Bite of the Burg, Football Practice, Freshman move-in, Hogue Ribbon Cutting, Intramural Fall Football, 2011- (Box-folder 41-51)
- Discover Disc 1: Leader Portrait, Discover #1, #2, 2011- (Box-folder 41-52)
- Latino Welcome, 2011- (Box-folder 41-53)
- Campus Fall: Students Walking Malls, Hebeler Tree shot with Students, 2011- (Box-folder 41-54)
- Wellington's Wildfire Campus Malls/2010/11 Nature: Winter, 2011 Spring, Water Shots (Box-folder 41-55)
- Student Appreciation Day, 2011- (Box-folder 41-56)
- Luau Dances, 2011- (Box-folder 41-57)
- Discover Disc 1: Discover #3 and #4, Rafting, 2011- (Box-folder 41-58)
- OPR outdoor Symposium Events 2010: 30-hour Fast T-Shirt Handout, ADA Ceremony-Gaudino Signing, Building Bridges, CareerQuest, Commencement Speaker Lunch, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 41-59)
- Spring Miscellaneous: Science and Stuarts with Turbines, Sun Shots, Music Building with McIntyre Sign, 2011- (Box-folder 41-60)
- Miscellaneous Spring: BlackHawk at Music/4 General and Gaudino, Dream Signing with Gaudino/Morrison, McIntyre Music Dedication, WMEA Hall of Fame Dedication, You and the Law Forum., 2011- (Box-folder 41-61)
- Miscellaneous Spring -Blast from the Past Dinner, Cinco De Mayo Dinner, Sam Reed/ Civic Engagement Lunch, Joya Malalai Speaking, WMEA State Comp at Music, 2011- (Box-folder 41-62)
- Miscellaneous Class/Speakers - 2004 Carbaugh, Bob, 2004-2011 (Box-folder 41-63)
- Fouts, Roger and Debbie, Melbourne, Tim and Flake, 02/2011 Rex, Panga-Morones, Enrique; Singh, Vijay, 2002-2011 (Box-folder 41-64)
- Eric Boles and Jon Kitna, 2011- (Box-folder 41-65)
- Barto Demolition/Historical Nicholson Cables with Sky, no date- (Box-folder 41-67)
- Miscellaneous Winter - 01/2011 Academic Recognition, 02/2011 Gaudino/Fred Meyer CEO Gift, 02/2011-03/2011 IET Building Construction Mardi Gras Dinner, 02/2011 MLK March (Box-folder 41-68)
- High School Music Camp, 10/2012 Camp Cohorts (Box-folder 41-69)
- Miscellaneous: 05/2012 College of Business Board Meeting, 05/2012 CWU at Lincoln Elementary, Dondji, 04/2012 Blaise Biology Class, 01/2012 Musica Antiqua Rehearsal, 04/2012 Taiko Drummers (Box-folder 41-70)
- Panga Field School - Disk 4: Devil's Lake, Oregon, 2012- (Box-folder 41-71)
- Source -Disc 1, 2012- (Box-folder 41-72)
- Source -Disk 2, 2012- (Box-folder 41-73)
- Panga Field School - Disk 3: Devil's Lake, Oregon, 2012- (Box-folder 41-74)
- Movers and Shakers N.S., 2008- (Box-folder 41-75)
- Miscellaneous Students - Orchestra in Blakes, Hometown Students, Mr. and Mrs. central Competition N.S., Homecoming Dance N.S., 2008- (Box-folder 41-76)
- Miscellaneous Nate Slover Shots - Cinco De Mayo, Jazz Brunch, Anjuman concert, Ballroom Concert, Recycle, Family Climbing/Rock Wall, 2008- (Box-folder 41-77)
- Student Village Kickoff, 2008- (Box-folder 41-78)
- Commencement Disk 3, 2008- (Box-folder 41-79)
- Commencement Disk 4, 2008- (Box-folder 41-80)
- Commencement Disk 5, 2008- (Box-folder 41-81)
- Aces, 2008- (Box-folder 41-82)
- Yakima River Clean Up!, 2008- (Box-folder 41-83)
- Douglas Honors College-Students Hanging Out, 2008- (Box-folder 41-84)
- Nate Slover Shots, Disc 4- 02/2008 Open Mic Night, Snow/ Students, SURC/Students, Volleyball I.M., 2007-2008 (Box-folder 41-85)
- Nate Slover Shots, 02/2008 Disc 5- Nate's Shots (General), Dorm Video Game Players, Snow, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 41-86)
- College of Business Board Room Meets Classroom05/2008- Advisory Board, Portraits (Box-folder 41-87)
- Snow MAUS, 2008- (Box-folder 41-88)
- Graduation, 2008- (Box-folder 41-89)
- Nate Slover Shots Disc - Studio Practice, Ken Munsell, Roxanne Easley, Laura Jones, Spring Color, Sweet Honey in the Rock, Track Meet, no date- (Box-folder 41-90)
- Nate Slover Shots 02/2008 Disc 6- Women in Sports Day, Percussion Concert, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 41-91)
- Miscellaneous Events - Accreditation Meeting, AFROTC MIA Vigil N.S., 2008- (Box-folder 41-92)
- - (Box-folder 41-93)
- America's Team Presentation Boo Central N.S., Dean Hall Opening Ceremony, Economic Forum N.S, Family Resource Center G.O., Goodenburger and Friends, no date - (Box-folder 41-94)
- Garden Japanese Incense Burners, 2008- (Box-folder 41-95)
- Hand Shots- Freshman, Challenge Course, OPR Paddle, Watermelon, IPOD, Wellington Paws, 2008- (Box-folder 41-96)
- Art Book Scans, Studio Book Shot, Concrete Textures, Snow Walkers, no date - (Box-folder 41-97)
- Boeing Jets in Flight, Seattle, 2008- (Box-folder 41-98)
- Conceptual -Hand Shots, Hand Writing, The Tav shirts/Hats Studio Shots, no date- (Box-folder 41-99)
- Conceptual-Hands on Aircraft, 2008- (Box-folder 41-100)
- Alpine Tower-Native American Summit N.S., no date- (Box-folder 41-101)
- Discover -Disk 1, 2008- (Box-folder 41-102)
- Discover Disc 2 Nate Shots Too-Rafting, 2008- (Box-folder 41-103)
- Discover Disk 3, 2008- (Box-folder 41-104)
- History Book Catering Food Shots, Mission Statement, Senate Resolution Document, Out of Focus Backgrounds, iPhone Shots, no date- (Box-folder 41-105)
- Miscellaneous -Studio Book Stack, Jongeward Desk, D50 Test Shots, Slover Focus Test, Reflections, RV Shots of Nate Slover, Hand Shots., 2008- (Box-folder 41-106)
- CWU Historical- Objects Studio Shots on White, no dates- (Box-folder 41-107)
- Snow MAUS, 2008- (Box-folder 41-108)
- Nate Slover Shots- Ware Fair/Orchesis, Snow/Students, Holiday Craft Fair, no date- (Box-folder 41-109)
- Goose Ridge Winery - Mumma and Hudelson, 2008- (Box-folder 41-110)
- McIntyre Crystal Ornament, Wildcat Reserve Wine, Hand Writing, You're In, $, Pledge, Central Pledge, no date- (Box-folder 41-111)
- Spring Campus-MAUS, Study, hangout, 2008- (Box-folder 41-112)
- Misc. Shots -C.A.M.P. Cohort Portrait, Central Transit New Vans, Dean Remodel Construction, Nature/ Solar/Recycle; Simpson Apt. Brooklane 1-12; Trammell Apt. Getz/Short 0-10 Skies, 2008- (Box-folder 41-113)
- Rock your Summer-Battle of Bands SURC, 2008- (Box-folder 41-114)
- Wenatchee Center Portraits and Classroom, 2008- (Box-folder 41-115)
- Orchesis Rehearsal, 2008- (Box-folder 41-116)
- EMT Students Hospitals/ Ambulance and Classroom, 2008- (Box-folder 41-117)
- Orchesis, 2008- (Box-folder 41-118)
- Commence Disc 1 2008 Commencement Disc 2 (Box-folder 41-119)
- Miscellaneous: Patuelli, Luca "Lazy legs, Retiree Reception, rich, Adrienne, Short Term Memory, Student Comm. Speaker, 2009- (Box-folder 41-120)
- CWU Stock Image Backup Disc 8: Sports, no date - (Box-folder 41-121)
- CWU Stock Image Backup Disc 9: Sports, no date - (Box-folder 41-122)
- CWU Stock Image Backup Disc 10: Sports, no date - (Box-folder 41-123)
- CWU Stock Image Backup Disc 11: Student Life, no date- (Box-folder 41-124)
- Conceptual: Writing on Hands, Out of Focus Shots (Creative), Sports Hand Shots, no date- (Box-folder 41-125)
- CWU Stock Image Backup Disc 1: Commencement, Dining, Learning/Classroom, Music, Residence Halls, River and Mountains, 2010- (Box-folder 41-126)
- CWU Stock Image Backup Disc 2: Odds and Ends, ROTC, Theater Arts, 2010- (Box-folder 41-127)
- CWU Stock Image BackUp Disc 3: Music Building, Portraits: Coaches, 2009 Police, President, Speakers, Wellington, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 41-128)
- CWU Stock Image BackUP Disc 4: 2002-2010 Administration Portraits (Box-folder 41-129)
- CWU Stock Image BackUP Disc 5: Portraits- Donors and Alumni, Employee of the Month, 2010- (Box-folder 41-130)
- CWU Stock Image BackUp Disc 6: Portraits- Faculty, 2010- (Box-folder 41-131)
- CWU Stock Image BackUp Disc 7: Portraits: Faculty, Staff, Students, Trustees, 2010- (Box-folder 41-132)
- CWU Stock Image BackUp Disc 12: Student Life, 2010- (Box-folder 41-133)
- CWU Stock Image BackUp Disc 13: Student Life, Campus Views/Architecture, 2010- (Box-folder 41-134)
- CWU Stock Image BackUp Disc 14: Campus and Regional Views/Architecture, 2010- (Box-folder 41-135)
- Events: Rock Against Rape, 2009 Source Picks, 2010 Source, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 41-136)
- Miscellaneous Events Disc 4: Tuition Protest, Rick Steves, 2010- (Box-folder 41-137)
- Miscellaneous Events Disc 3: Orchesis Rehearsal, Percussion Concert, Presidential Address to staff; Salbi, Zainab, 2010- (Box-folder 41-138)
- Miscellaneous: Brooklane Apartment Interior, 2010 Wildcat Day (Box-folder 41-139)
- Athletic Hall of Fame Banquet: 04/2009 Frederick Field Dedication (Box-folder 41-140)
- Campus Events/ Campus, 02/2009 Chanticleer, CopyCat Shop, Hip-Hop Video shoot in Nicholson Pavilion, 02/2009 Mardi Gras Dinner, Nicholson Pavilion Interior with Game, Parking Signs, Science and Black Halls, Science Wind Sculpture, Snow, Award Winning Teachers Panel, 02/2009 Wenatchee Center Gaudino Welcome, 02/2009 Judy Yu-final Board Meeting (Box-folder 41-141)
- Human Rights Awareness Week Disc 1, 2009- (Box-folder 41-142)
- Human Rights Awareness Week Disc 2, 2009- (Box-folder 41-143)
- Homecoming Football and Wildfire, 2009- (Box-folder 41-144)
- Miscellaneous Spring First Amendment Festival, 2009- (Box-folder 41-145)
- Family weekend, Gaer- Carlton Kathy USAF Award, 2008 Jazz in the Valley: Unknown Photography, Jazz Combo Nite N.S., Klugh Earl, Locks of Love, 05/2009 Orchesis, Rockin' BBQ (Box-folder 41-146)
- Happy Diverse Student Group: 02/2009 Gaudino Meeting: Zenza Camera Concept Shots (Box-folder 41-147)
- Student Appreciation Day, 2009- (Box-folder 41-148)
- ROTC President's Review, 2009- (Box-folder 41-149)
- Miscellaneous Events: Art Department N.S., Deep Daze, Man-Up Panel Discussion, MLK March (Gaudino), 3.7 GPA Awards N.S., Biology Students N.S., Majors Fair N.S., C.O.B. Pro Development Day N.S., Sherman Alexie, 2009- (Box-folder 41-150)
- Thriller Dance REH. and Performance at SURC, C.O.B. Adding Machine Studio, no date - (Box-folder 41-151)
- Discover, 2009- (Box-folder 41-152)
- Lynnwood Des Moines: Building/Students, Professors/Classroom, 2009- (Box-folder 41-153)
- Spring Campus, 2009- (Box-folder 41-154)
- U.S. Flag in the Wind: Household items, ROTC Patches, no date- (Box-folder 41-155)
- President Gaudino with iPhone, Laser Light Show, 2009- (Box-folder 41-156)
- Barge Hall Flags, Dean Hall Art Twilight, Shaw-Smyser Column Twilight, 2009- (Box-folder 41-157)
- President Gaudino Welcomes: SURC/ Art Walk, 2009- (Box-folder 41-158)
- President Gaudino: Budget Presentations, 2009- (Box-folder 41-159)
- President Gaudino Inauguration Disc 1, 2009- (Box-folder 41-160)
- President Gaudino Inauguration disc 2, 2009- (Box-folder 41-161)
- Source: World language Day, 2009- (Box-folder 41-162)
- President Gaudino -Board of Trustees Meeting, Flood Photos 01/2009, 2002-2009 (Box-folder 41-163)
- Alumni- Foundation, Homecoming Events: Awards Banquet, Cat's Den, Tailgating, 2009- (Box-folder 41-164)
- D.O.A. Ribbon Cut, Hill Hall G.O., Hogue Groundbreak, Michoacán CWU Signing, Purser Hall Dedication, no date- (Box-folder 41-165)
- Bite of Eburg: Clubs BBQ, Cosby, Dean Hall Art Dedication, Governor Gregoire, Imani Winds, Model T's, Museum of CRE Ribbon cut, Road Trip Nation, Vet Center Open, no date- (Box-folder 41-166)
- McConnell: Stage w/spot, Giant Tiff file, no date- (Box-folder 41-167)
- Globe: Envelope, Studio Shots, no date- (Box-folder 41-168)
- Hats! Disc 1: Student Names in "Portraits", "Students", 2009- (Box-folder 41-169)
- Hats! Disc 2: Student Names on this Disc, 2009- (Box-folder 41-170)
- Mace with Sky Runner Shoes in Motion, 2008- (Box-folder 41-171)
- RecCenter Basketball: Running Feet 9, 2008- (Box-folder 41-172)
- Nate Slover Shots: Disc 3: Fishbowl Study, Basketball, Fraser/HAAS Perf., 2007-2008 (Box-folder 41-173)
- C.O.B. Econ 101 for Visiting High Schoolers CWU Students, 2008- (Box-folder 41-174)
- Nate Slover Pics: Gallery One, Jazz Combo Night:, 2008- (Box-folder 41-175)
- Miscellaneous: Anderson B-11, Getz/ Short D-10 (Trammell), C.O.B. Economics 101 for Visiting H.S., N.S. Ping Pong Shots, N.S. Students at SURC, Recital Hall Shots, 2008- (Box-folder 41-176)
- Little Cats Summer Day Camp N.S. 08/2008 (Box-folder 41-177)
- Nate Shots: Kid's Rock, 3 on 3 tournament, Badminton Disc 2, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 41-178)
- Meet your R.A.'s, Wangari MAATHAI, State of Diversity, 2008- (Box-folder 41-179)
- Miscellaneous Artbook Re-Scans, Blewitt Pass, Concrete Textures, Central Transit Van, Shaw Smyser NE Entry, Survey Students on Lawn, Wildhorse Wind Farm, Prof. Wood with PSE 1-Disc 2, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 41-180)
- Alumni Events: Excellence in Teaching, 05/2008Farewell for Now, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 41-181)
- AHOP Banquet Nate Slover, 2008- (Box-folder 41-182)
- Beethoven's 9th concert-Nate Slover: C.A.M.P. Banquet-Villacres, no date- (Box-folder 41-183)
- E.M.T. Students, KVCH/Ambulance and Classroom, 2008- (Box-folder 41-184)
- Nate Shots Disc 1 Fishbowl Study, Indoor Soccer, Deep Sea Daze, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 41-185)
- Miscellaneous Nate Slover Shots: Building Bridges, Open Mic Night, Spinner/Yoga Classes, 2008- (Box-folder 41-186)
- Meaningful Connections: Psychology Students with Seniors at Hearthstone Cottage, 2008- (Box-folder 41-187)
- Central Connections: D'Aquisto, L.; Christian, T/Smart,C. Emmy, Fudacz, R.; History Book Studio Shot; Horsley, J.; Mission Statement Studio Shots., Jeri's Senate Res. Studio Shots, 2008- (Box-folder 41-188)
- Salman Rushdie, 2008- (Box-folder 41-189)
- Miscellaneous: President's Gala, Residence Hall Construction Kickoff, ROTC Ranger Challenge, Waters Shots by Ian Quitadamo, 2008- (Box-folder 41-190)
- HANOS Search Piece, Raw Captures, 2008- (Box-folder 41-191)
- Hands and Faces (Search Piece), 2008- (Box-folder 41-192)
- Search Piece Imagery, 2008- (Box-folder 41-193)
- Beacon Allyne Suzanne Dantzler-Drobnack, Wolfgang Franz, Nancy Graeber-Pidgeon, Richard "Moose" Mack, Mark Pritchard, Ravae Rossmaier, Rodney Champaco, 2008- (Box-folder 41-194)
- Application: Rez Life, 2008- (Box-folder 41-195)
- Fall: Central Connections, Acceptance, Beacon, President's Report, 2008- (Box-folder 41-196)
- Men's Basketball "Whiteout": ESPN Game, 2011- (Box-folder 42-1)